[
    {
        "Subject": "Rekenen",
        "Progresslevel": 0,
        "Type": "ConnectQTOA",
        "QuestionsAndAnswers": [
            {
                "Question": "3+2",
                "Answer": "5"
            },
            {
                "Question": "5+11",
                "Answer": "16"
            },
            {
                "Question": "3+8",
                "Answer": "11"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "Subject": "Rekenen",
        "Progresslevel": 1,
        "Type": "ConnectQTOA",
        "QuestionsAndAnswers": [
            {
                "Question": "3+6",
                "Answer": "9"
            },
            {
                "Question": "5+11",
                "Answer": "16"
            },
            {
                "Question": "3+2",
                "Answer": "5"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "Subject": "Rekenen",
        "Progresslevel": 2,
        "Type": "ConnectQTOA",
        "QuestionsAndAnswers": [
            {
                "Question": "4+7",
                "Answer": "11"
            },
            {
                "Question": "6+12",
                "Answer": "18"
            },
            {
                "Question": "4+3",
                "Answer": "7"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "Subject": "Rekenen",
        "Progresslevel": 3,
        "Type": "ConnectQTOA",
        "QuestionsAndAnswers": [
            {
                "Question": "5+8",
                "Answer": "13"
            },
            {
                "Question": "7+13",
                "Answer": "20"
            },
            {
                "Question": "5+4",
                "Answer": "9"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "Subject": "Rekenen",
        "Progresslevel": 4,
        "Type": "ConnectQTOA",
        "QuestionsAndAnswers": [
            {
                "Question": "6+9",
                "Answer": "15"
            },
            {
                "Question": "8+14",
                "Answer": "22"
            },
            {
                "Question": "6+5",
                "Answer": "11"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "Subject": "Rekenen",
        "Progresslevel": 5,
        "Type": "ConnectQTOA",
        "QuestionsAndAnswers": [
            {
                "Question": "7+10",
                "Answer": "17"
            },
            {
                "Question": "9+15",
                "Answer": "24"
            },
            {
                "Question": "7+6",
                "Answer": "13"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "Subject": "Rekenen",
        "Progresslevel": 6,
        "Type": "ConnectQTOA",
        "QuestionsAndAnswers": [
            {
                "Question": "8+11",
                "Answer": "19"
            },
            {
                "Question": "10+16",
                "Answer": "26"
            },
            {
                "Question": "8+7",
                "Answer": "15"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "Subject": "Rekenen",
        "Progresslevel": 7,
        "Type": "ConnectQTOA",
        "QuestionsAndAnswers": [
            {
                "Question": "2+3",
                "Answer": "5"
            },
            {
                "Question": "4+1",
                "Answer": "5"
            },
            {
                "Question": "1+1",
                "Answer": "2"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "Subject": "Rekenen",
        "Progresslevel": 8,
        "Type": "ConnectQTOA",
        "QuestionsAndAnswers": [
            {
                "Question": "5+3",
                "Answer": "8"
            },
            {
                "Question": "2+7",
                "Answer": "9"
            },
            {
                "Question": "6+2",
                "Answer": "8"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "Subject": "Rekenen",
        "Progresslevel": 9,
        "Type": "ConnectQTOA",
        "QuestionsAndAnswers": [
            {
                "Question": "7+5",
                "Answer": "12"
            },
            {
                "Question": "3+6",
                "Answer": "9"
            },
            {
                "Question": "4+8",
                "Answer": "12"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "Subject": "Rekenen",
        "Progresslevel": 10,
        "Type": "ConnectQTOA",
        "QuestionsAndAnswers": [
            {
                "Question": "8+4",
                "Answer": "12"
            },
            {
                "Question": "9+6",
                "Answer": "15"
            },
            {
                "Question": "5+7",
                "Answer": "12"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "Subject": "Taal",
        "Progresslevel": 1,
        "Type": "ConnectQTOA",
        "QuestionsAndAnswers": [
            {
                "Question": "juist",
                "Answer": "onjuist"
            },
            {
                "Question": "achter",
                "Answer": "voor"
            },
            {
                "Question": "ander",
                "Answer": "soortgelijk"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "Subject": "Taal",
        "Progresslevel": 0,
        "Type": "ConnectQTOA",
        "QuestionsAndAnswers": [
            {
                "Question": "juist",
                "Answer": "onjuist"
            },
            {
                "Question": "achter",
                "Answer": "voor"
            },
            {
                "Question": "ander",
                "Answer": "soortgelijk"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "Subject": "Taal",
        "Progresslevel": 2,
        "Type": "ConnectQTOA",
        "QuestionsAndAnswers": [
            {
                "Question": "fout",
                "Answer": "correct"
            },
            {
                "Question": "boven",
                "Answer": "onder"
            },
            {
                "Question": "gelijk",
                "Answer": "verschillend"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "Subject": "Taal",
        "Progresslevel": 3,
        "Type": "ConnectQTOA",
        "QuestionsAndAnswers": [
            {
                "Question": "vóór",
                "Answer": "na"
            },
            {
                "Question": "binnen",
                "Answer": "buiten"
            },
            {
                "Question": "hetzelfde",
                "Answer": "verschillend"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "Subject": "Taal",
        "Progresslevel": 4,
        "Type": "ConnectQTOA",
        "QuestionsAndAnswers": [
            {
                "Question": "voor",
                "Answer": "na"
            },
            {
                "Question": "rechts",
                "Answer": "links"
            },
            {
                "Question": "identiek",
                "Answer": "verschillend"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "Subject": "Taal",
        "Progresslevel": 5,
        "Type": "ConnectQTOA",
        "QuestionsAndAnswers": [
            {
                "Question": "onderste",
                "Answer": "bovenste"
            },
            {
                "Question": "gelijkwaardig",
                "Answer": "ongelijk"
            },
            {
                "Question": "eerst",
                "Answer": "laatst"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "Subject": "Taal",
        "Progresslevel": 6,
        "Type": "ConnectQTOA",
        "QuestionsAndAnswers": [
            {
                "Question": "klein",
                "Answer": "groot"
            },
            {
                "Question": "dik",
                "Answer": "dun"
            },
            {
                "Question": "lang",
                "Answer": "kort"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "Subject": "Taal",
        "Progresslevel": 7,
        "Type": "ConnectQTOA",
        "QuestionsAndAnswers": [
            {
                "Question": "zwart",
                "Answer": "wit"
            },
            {
                "Question": "zwaar",
                "Answer": "licht"
            },
            {
                "Question": "hoog",
                "Answer": "laag"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "Subject": "Taal",
        "Progresslevel": 8,
        "Type": "ConnectQTOA",
        "QuestionsAndAnswers": [
            {
                "Question": "moeilijk",
                "Answer": "gemakkelijk"
            },
            {
                "Question": "snel",
                "Answer": "traag"
            },
            {
                "Question": "nat",
                "Answer": "droog"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "Subject": "Taal",
        "Progresslevel": 9,
        "Type": "ConnectQTOA",
        "QuestionsAndAnswers": [
            {
                "Question": "oud",
                "Answer": "nieuw"
            },
            {
                "Question": "warm",
                "Answer": "koud"
            },
            {
                "Question": "sterk",
                "Answer": "zwak"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "Subject": "Taal",
        "Progresslevel": 10,
        "Type": "ConnectQTOA",
        "QuestionsAndAnswers": [
            {
                "Question": "glad",
                "Answer": "ruw"
            },
            {
                "Question": "vol",
                "Answer": "leeg"
            },
            {
                "Question": "hard",
                "Answer": "zacht"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "Subject": "verkeer",
        "Progresslevel": 1,
        "Type": "verkeer",
        "QuestionsAndAnswers": []
    },
    {
        "Subject": "Engels",
        "Progresslevel": 1,
        "Type": "testgame",
        "QuestionsAndAnswers": [
          {
            "Question": "Dog",
            "Answer": "Hond"
          },
          {
            "Question": "Empty",
            "Answer": "Leeg"
          },
          {
            "Question": "House",
            "Answer": "Huis"
          }
        ]
    }
] 